Classicthesis Typographic Thesis

This template has been designed as a homage to the elements of typographic style. As such, it has an air of efficiency and optimal design. It is suitable for any high-level degree thesis such as for a PhD, Masters or Honors. Sections within the thesis are clearly separated in a consistent way, as are sections within each chapter. The default structure of the thesis proceeds in the following order: title page, dedication, abstract, publications, acknowledgements, contents, list of tables/figures/listings, acronyms, content chapters, appendices, bibliography, colophon and declaration.

The template includes a chapter to get you started using the template and provides several useful suggestions which are worth reading. Also included are two chapters showing the capability of the template to give an idea of how it will look with your content.

===================================================

Original sources: https://www.latextemplates.com/template/classicthesis-typographic-thesis
Author:           André Miede (http://www.miede.de) with commenting modifications by Vel
License:          GNU General Public License (v2)

Status:           added by Papeeria Team, maintenance on demand
Last update:      29 Mar 2017 